<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | CRUISE</title>
    <link>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:43:16 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/images/icon_hua992cb10085e06a51eab2da50465a284_10796_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory data mining and context-aware intent recognition</title>
      <link>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/trajectory_modelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:43:16 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/trajectory_modelling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our research was one of the very first work ever done internationally in trajectory monitoring and mining for collision avoidance. Vehicle trajectory and manoeuvres were monitored and mined in order to extract collision patterns in road intersections from near collision events. The extracted patterns were used to detect conflicting intentions early on, prior to entering intersections, and for collision warning to be issued. The collision pattern mining, detection, and warning framework managed to issue collision warning 3-4 seconds earlier than the baseline mathematical models, which was significant in the area of collision avoidance, and could make the difference between life and death in real-world situations.
This work was cited multiple times by the same group of researchers from UC Berkeley’s Intelligent Transportation Systems and Robotics department and Mercedes Benz R&amp;amp;D centre, who followed the idea from Dr. Salim’s papers further to develop their own risk assessment at road intersections. The work was also cited by autonomous vehicle researchers from Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), signal processing researchers from University of Washington, and a mobile network researcher from National Cheng Kung University who developed his own collision warning apparatus which was patented in 2016. The work also inspired the recent patent “Autonomous Vehicle Control System” by Northrop Grumman Corporations (20170097640), which leads to a collaboration funded by Northrop Grumman Corporations.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Context and community modelling using proximity signal</title>
      <link>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/context_community_modelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 15:42:51 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kaiqinchi.github.io/project/context_community_modelling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have published our research outcomes on fundamental and practical time-series and spatio-temporal data mining and machine learning techniques which can be applied on multiple types of data from sensors, Internet of Things, and social media in the domain of smart cities, smart buildings, smart parking, and intelligent transportation systems. I have been awarded nationally competitive grants and numerous industry contracts, with the total amount awarded of over than 3M in the last 5 years. Nine out of ten of my research grants are funded collaborations with government agencies or industry, with practical applications such as indoor monitoring and analytics in university and retail environments, driving behaviour recognition, road risk analysis, and passenger movement analysis in airports. In my project with local and state governments, I developed new approaches for spatio-temporal aggregation and retrieval of urban data, and clustering heterogeneous urban data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our research has generated context-aware and personalised models for journey planning. Our work has generated research contributions in analysis, prediction, and personalised profiling of multiple types of trajectories (e.g. human, public transports, private cars, airplanes) from a wide range of datasets from smartphones, wireless infrastructures, sensors, and Internet of Things. We have proposed a novel contour-based accessibility aware route planning algorithm for the mobility impaired, solving the first / last mile problem while traveling on multi-modal transportation network.  We have also developed data-driven predictive trip planning models for taxi passengers and drivers. An accurate taxi wait time prediction model has been tested using large-scale taxi trajectory logs from New York City.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
